<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelogs>
    <changelog>
        <element>pkg_jtseo</element>
        <type>package</type>
        <version>1.0.62</version>

        <security>
            <item>No security fixes.</item>
        </security>

        <fix>
            <item>Added the Joomla changelog URL to the package manifest so the Extensions: Manage version modal can be displayed.</item>
            <item>Added external update and changelog metadata templates for the public update server.</item>
            <item>Updated package, component and plugin versions to 1.0.62.</item>
            <item>Added database update marker for version 1.0.62.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>pkg_jtseo</element>
        <type>package</type>
        <version>1.0.61</version>

        <security>
            <item>No security fixes.</item>
        </security>

        <fix>
            <item>Improved 404 logging reliability for Joomla routing edge cases.</item>
            <item>Fixed misleading dashboard status indicators for the Redirects / 404 section.</item>
            <item>Replaced the technical 404 log table health-check label with clearer status information.</item>
            <item>Separated the actual 404 logging status from database table availability checks.</item>
            <item>Improved detection of modified article URLs that may resolve unexpectedly through Joomla routing.</item>
            <item>Updated package, component and plugin versions to 1.0.61.</item>
            <item>Added database update marker for version 1.0.61.</item>
        </fix>

        <change>
            <item>Refined the Redirects / 404 dashboard interface for clearer user feedback.</item>
        </change>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>pkg_jtseo</element>
        <type>package</type>
        <version>1.0.57</version>

        <security>
            <item>No security fixes.</item>
        </security>

        <fix>
            <item>Added the missing COM_JTSEO_CONFIGURATION language string.</item>
            <item>Fixed the Joomla Options page title showing the raw language key.</item>
            <item>Updated package, component and plugin versions to 1.0.57.</item>
            <item>Added database update marker for version 1.0.57.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>pkg_jtseo</element>
        <type>package</type>
        <version>1.0.56</version>

        <security>
            <item>No security fixes.</item>
        </security>

        <addition>
            <item>Added pagination options to the Bulk Meta Manager.</item>
            <item>Added a default Needs attention filter for low-score articles.</item>
            <item>Added expandable advanced metadata fields in the Bulk Meta Manager.</item>
            <item>Added privacy-friendly 404 logging options for query strings, referrers and user agents.</item>
            <item>Added database update marker for version 1.0.56.</item>
        </addition>

        <change>
            <item>Improved the Bulk Meta Manager layout for a cleaner editing workflow.</item>
            <item>Collapsed CSV Import / Export tools by default to reduce dashboard clutter.</item>
            <item>Changed the Bulk Meta Manager save button text to better describe the action.</item>
            <item>Improved responsive behavior for search, filter and reset controls.</item>
            <item>Updated package, component and plugin versions to 1.0.56.</item>
            <item>Updated README documentation for the public stable release.</item>
            <item>Improved English and Turkish language strings.</item>
        </change>

        <fix>
            <item>Optimized 404 logging to avoid unnecessary database writes on normal frontend page views.</item>
            <item>Fixed Bulk Meta Manager button wrapping on narrow layouts.</item>
            <item>Improved dashboard support link handling when optional URLs are empty.</item>
            <item>Improved package integrity and update metadata consistency.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>

    <changelog>
        <element>pkg_jtseo</element>
        <type>package</type>
        <version>1.0.53</version>

        <security>
            <item>No security fixes.</item>
        </security>

        <fix>
            <item>Added GPL license copies to package and child extension archives.</item>
            <item>Cleaned the SQL update chain to avoid duplicate-column errors on mixed upgrade paths.</item>
            <item>Added safe component installer schema alignment for redirect and 404 log tables.</item>
            <item>Moved Structured Data dashboard mapping messages to language strings.</item>
            <item>Removed deprecated asset fallback calls from the content plugin.</item>
            <item>Updated README version and privacy note.</item>
            <item>Clarified BreadcrumbList mapping copy for Joomla core Breadcrumbs module and duplicate JSON-LD checks.</item>
            <item>Added optional Support / Community dashboard card with configurable project, GitHub and support links.</item>
        </fix>
    </changelog>
</changelogs>
